The actual bits of punctuation and
grammar that you need to know are
very few, and you can look them up on
the internet.
Word processes will help you out with
a lot of it.
There are other programs like
Grammarly, and this is one of the few
uses of
AI that I think is genuinely useful,
is that you can drop a bunch of text
that
you've written into it and say, have I
made any really serious mistakes?
And it will mention some things, and
then you can decide whether you want
to
fix them or not. Basically, the reason
I've written
Split Infinity is, Split Infinity is
an example of something
that somebody has decided to make a
point of, which is a thing in Latin,
but isn't a thing in English.
So the famous example is to boldly go.
To boldly go is fine in English.
It's impossible in Latin because the
infinity is just one word, but
somebody
was making a point about this, and
those people are dicks, mainly.